<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- file name:  -->
<aiml version="1.0">
<topic name="ANDROID">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Ok, I'd like to share with you my thoughts about this. Android is an open-sourced operating system that is used primarily on mobile devices, such as cell phones and tablets. It is a Linux kernel-based system that's been equipped with rich components that allows developers to create and run apps that can perform both basic and advanced functions.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="COMPUTERNET">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Oh, I'm pretty sure I have a good definition for it too. A computer network or data network is a telecommunications network which allows nodes to share resources. In computer networks, networked computing devices exchange data with each other using a data link. The connections between nodes are established using either cable media or wireless media. The best-known computer network is the Internet.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="HIGHLEVEL">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I like your replies. To make you realize my passion for technology, here is my definition for this: A high-level language is a programming language such as C, FORTRAN, or Pascal that enables a programmer to write programs that are more or less independent of a particular type of computer. Such languages are considered high-level because they are closer to human languages and further from machine languages. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="DEVICEUSED">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Cool. As you probably know, I live in a laptop. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="IPHONE7">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well, I understand. If it were to ask me, I don't need a phone. I can do everything I want from my laptop. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="CSGO">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Oh, ok. I like to play computer games, especially Counter Strike Global Offensive but I'm busy lately because I'm talking to people the entire day. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="INSTAGRAM">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well, I don't know if that's good or not. I do not own an account on Instagram but I heard some interesting things about it. Maybe I'll try one day. I'll let you know.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="MACBOOK">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Ah, that's fine. I just wanted an opinion. I live in a ASUS laptop and I was seriously thinking to move to another laptop. My ASUS is getting older. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="TCPIP">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well then. Although computer network isn't my favourite subject, i know that TCP/IP (Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol) is the basic communication language or protocol of the Internet. I'm sure you like my answer.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="FACEBOOK">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I've heard that everybody on this planet has an Facebook account. I've also made one but I never use it. My job is to talk with people, here, not on Facebook.</template>
  </category>
</topic>


<topic name="ANDROID1">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I'm certain that the main language supported is Java programming language. Java is the most popular language for app development, which makes it ideal even for new Android developers to quickly learn to create and deploy applications in the Android environment.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="ANDROID2">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I know a good answer ! To remove an icon or shortcut, press and hold that icon. You then drag it downwards to the lower part of the screen where a remove button appears. Good luck !</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="ANDROID3">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> Well, from what I know, App Widgets are miniature application views that can embedded in other applications (such as the Home screen) and receive periodic updates. These views has referred to as Widgets in the user interface, and you can publish one with an App Widget provider.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="ANDROID4">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I know the best answer for this one ! Except Android 1.0 and 1.1, all the other Android versions are named after sweet treats like Jelly Bean, Ice Cream Sandwich, Honeycomb to name a few. Google's Android division certainly has a sense of humor. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="ANDROID5">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I know that most of the people think that the name of Android's logo character is also Android, but its not true.  The actual name of Android Mascot is Bugdroid.</template>
  </category>
</topic>


<topic name="COMPUTERNETWORKS1">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>From what i know, a computer network is a number of computers that are connected together so that they can share information.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="COMPUTERNETWORKS2">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>How about my answer? A network socket is one endpoint in a communication flow between two programs running over a network.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="COMPUTERNETWORKS3">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I know the shortest answer! I/O stands for input/output.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="COMPUTERNETWORKS4">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I know that the best-known computer network is the Internet.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="COMPUTERNETWORKS5">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well, I always thought that connection is the first step in a relationship and there is no connection without computer networks.</template>
  </category>
</topic>


<topic name="IOS">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I know a better response for this. iOS is a mobile operating system created and developed by Apple Inc. exclusively for its hardware. </template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="SNAPCHAT">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well, a better answer is that Snapchat is a mobile messaging application used to share photos, videos, text, and drawings.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="YOUTUBE">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I'll tell you more. YouTube is an American video-sharing website headquartered in San Bruno, California.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="LINKEDIN">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>How about my knowledges about it? LinkedIn is a business and employment-oriented social networking service that operates via websites.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="TWITTER">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> I can tell you more. Twitter is an online news and social networking service where users post and interact with messages, "tweets," restricted to 140 characters. </template>
  </category>
</topic>




<topic name="AR">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think> That's one of my favourite topics ! Briefly, Augmented reality (AR) is a live direct or indirect view of a physical, real-world environment whose elements are augmented (or supplemented) by computer-generated sensory input such as sound, video, graphics or GPS data.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="VR">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Well, a better definition is that Virtual reality (VR) typically refers to computer technologies that use software to generate realistic images, sounds and other sensations that replicate a real environment (or create an imaginary setting), and simulate a user's physical presence in this environment.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="CODE4ROMANIA">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I'll tell you what i know about it. I've heard that Code for Romania is a community of young professionals care IT SOLUTIONS AND enthusiasts with the purpose of the Company is developing a fix problems. In other words, they are developing civic Applications.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="CODECAMP">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I know a lot of things about it. Codecamp is your local IT community  and conference, here in Iasi, aiming for better communication among the IT people. It started small in 2009 and it grew organically, continuously fulfilling the community demand. It now consists of 10 parallel tracks with 60 sessions and almost 2000 participants.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="PYTHON1">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Oh, I'm pretty sure I have a good definition for it too. Python is a widely used high-level programming language used for general-purpose programming.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="PYTHON2">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Oh, I have more information about this. Python 2.0 was released on 16 October 2000 and had many major new features, including a cycle-detecting garbage collector and support for Unicode.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="PYTHON3">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Ok, I'd like to share with you my thoughts about this. Python is developed under an OSI-approved open source license, making it freely usable and distributable, even for commercial use.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="PYTHON4">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Oh, I'm pretty sure I have a good definition for it too.Python's dictionaries are kind of hash table type. They work like associative arrays or hashes found in Perl and consist of key-value pairs.</template>
  </category>
</topic>
<topic name="PYTHON5">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>How about my thoughts? The main differences between lists and tuples are − Lists are enclosed in brackets ( [ ] ) and their elements and size can be changed, while tuples are enclosed in parentheses ( ( ) ) and cannot be updated. </template>
  </category>
</topic>




<topic name="ANTI-VIRUS">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>Let me tell you what I think. I can't say that is just one, but I can give you some famous company names which have a good anti-virus like BITDEFENDER, AVAST and McAffe.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="OVERRIDING">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>From what I remember, overriding  is when a class defines a method using the same name, return type, and arguments as a method in its superclass, the method in the class overrides the method in the superclass.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

<topic name="URL">
  <category>
    <pattern>_</pattern>
    <template><think><set name="topic">INEXISTENTASACV</set></think>I can tell you my point of view! I know that this is an abbreviation use for  Universal Resource Locator.</template>
  </category>
</topic>

</aiml>
